Robert A. Taft Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Political File, 1924-1953 (Box 99-471)
  - 1952 (Box 320)
    - State file
      - New York
        - General correspondence
          - M-Q, (7 folders) (Box 381)
          - R-S, (4 folders) (Box 382)
          - S-Z, (8 folders) (Box 383)
        - Clubs (Box 384)
        - Colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Contributions
          - Received
          - Requested
        - Correspondence, (3 folders) (Box 385)
        - County chairmen
        - Credentials
        - Delegates
        - Key men
        - Publicity
        - Questionnaires (Box 386)
        - Selvage, James P.
        - Senator's letter
        - State officials
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Talbot, Harold
        - Thank- you letters
          - After trip
          - After 29 Club Dinner (Box 387)
        - “Urging to Run” answered
        - Young Republicans
      - North Carolina
        - General correspondence
          - A-N, (2 folders)
          - O-Z, (2 folders) (Box 388)
        - Colleges and Young Republicans
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists
        - Questionnaires
        - State officers
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
      - North Dakota
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Addresses
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Questionnaires (Box 389)
        - State officers and officers of State
          - Central Committee
          - Supporters of Taft
          - Thank- you letters
      - Norway
      - Ohio
        - General correspondence
          - A-C, (7 folders)
          - D-I, (8 folders) (Box 390)
          - J-Mc, (6 folders) (Box 391)
          - N-S, (6 folders) (Box 392)
          - T-Z, (5 folders) (Box 393)
        - Clubs
        - Colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Correspondence, (2 folders) (Box 394)
        - Delegates lists, (2 folders)
        - Delegation returns
        - Dentists
        - Hollister, John B.
        - List and thank-you letters after trip
        - Pearson, Drew
        - Primary and convention dates (Box 395)
        - Questionnaires, (2 folders)
        - Republican Party officials
        - Shives, George A.
        - State officers, (2 folders)
        - Supporters of Taft, (2 folders)
        - Survey (Box 396)
        - Taft pins
        - “Urging to Run” answered
        - Women's Brigade
        - Young Republicans
      - Oklahoma
        - General correspondence
          - A-G
          - H-Z, (3 folders)
        - Clubs and colleges (Box 397)
        - Confidential
        - Delegate lists
        - Key men and survey
        - List and thank-you letters after trip
        - Questionnaires
        - State officials
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Oregon
        - General correspondence, A-Z (Box 398)
        - Congratulatory
        - Credential (Box 399)
        - Delegate lists
        - State officers and officers of State Central Committee
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Pennsylvania
        - General correspondence
          - A-E, (6 folders)
          - F-M, (6 folders) (Box 400)
          - Mc-Z, (9 folders) (Box 401)
        - Clubs (Box 402)
        - Colleges
        - Congratulatory
        - Contributions
          - Received
          - Requested
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
        - Delegates lists
        - Key men, (2 folders) (Box 403)
        - State officers
        - Supporters of Taft, (2 folders)
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters after trip
        - “Urging to Run” answered
        - Young Republicans (Box 404)
      - Philippines
      - Puerto Rico
        - Correspondence
        - Credentials
      - Rhode Island
        - General correspondence, A-W, (2 folders)
        - Correspondence
        - Delegate list
        - List and thank-you letters after trip
        - State officers and officers of State Central Committee
        - Supporters of Taft
      - South America
      - South Carolina
        - General correspondence
          - A-R, (2 folders)
          - S-Z (Box 405)
        - Congratulatory
        - Delegate lists
        - State officers and officers of State Central Committee
        - Supporters of Taft
      - South Dakota
        - General correspondence, A-W, (4 folders)
        - Clubs
        - Correspondence
        - Delegate lists
        - Questionnaires (Box 406)
        - Senator's letters
        - State officers and officers of State Central Committee
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Tennessee
        - General correspondence
          - A-O, (3 folders)
          - P-Z, (2 folders) (Box 407)
        - Congratulatory
        - Delegate list
        - Eisenhower, Dwight D., general program
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Texas
        - General correspondence
          - A-B, (2 folders)
          - B-H, (5 folders) (Box 408)
          - I-R, (5 folders) (Box 409)
          - S-Z, (3 folders) (Box 410)
        - Clubs and Young Republicans
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegate list
        - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Utah (Box 411)
        - General correspondence, A-W
        - Correspondence
        - Delegate list
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
      - Vermont
        - General correspondence
          - A-L
          - M-V (Box 412)
        - Delegate list
        - Speech by Taft, Borne, Vt.
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Virginia
        - General correspondence
          - A-R, (4 folders)
          - S-Z, (2 folders) (Box 413)
        - Correspondence
        - Delegate list
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip
      - Virgin Islands
      - Washington
        - General correspondence
          - A-D
          - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 414)
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegate list, (2 folders) (Box 415)
        - Senator's letters
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters after trip
        - Young Republicans
      - West Virginia
        - General correspondence
          - A-H, (4 folders)
          - I-Z, (2 folders) (Box 416)
        - Congratulatory
        - Credentials
        - Delegate list
        - Questionnaires
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Thank-you letters after trip
        - Young Republicans
      - Wisconsin (Box 417)
        - General correspondence
          - A-G, (6 folders)
          - H-S, (6 folders) (Box 418)
          - T-Z (Box 419)
        - Correspondence, (2 folders)
        - Delegates
        - Doctors
        - Form letters, (3 folders)
        - Questionnaires (Box 420)
        - School lists
        - Speech, Wausau, Wis.
        - State officers, and officers of State Central Committee
        - Supporters of Taft, (2 folders)
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters
          - After trip to Wisconsin
      - Wyoming
        - General correspondence
          - A-K
          - L-W (Box 421)
        - Credentials
        - Delegate lists
        - Supporters of Taft
        - Survey
        - Thank-you letters after trip
        - Young Republicans
    - Subject file
      - Addresses, thank-you letters
      - Agriculture, (2 folders)
      - Airlines
      - Alphabetical file (Box 422)
        - Special
          - Broadcasting networks, controversy with
          - Correspondence
          - Dirksen, Everett M.
          - District of Columbia
          - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
          - Emanuel, Victor
          - Goodwin, Bill
          - Headquarters
            - Hampton, Margaret
            - Mailing department
            - Publicity
            - Reeves, Mildred
          - Howard, Perry
          - Individuals
          - Klein, Julius
          - Literature receipts
          - Senator's letters
          - Shroyer, Tom
          - Warner, Milo
        - States
          - Alabama-Missouri
          - Nebraska-Wyoming
        - Miscellany (Box 423)
          - General correspondence
            - A-Mc, (6 folders)
            - H-Z, (4 folders) (Box 424)
          - Adams, Sherman
          - Buffett, Howard
          - Byoir, Carl
          - Chicago, Ill., convention plan
          - Colegrave letter
          - Committee
            - Brown, Clarence J.
            - Brown, Katherine Kennedy
            - Citizens (Box 425)
            - Coleman, Thomas E.
            - Davies, Mrs. Preston
            - Hamilton, John D. M.
            - Ingalls, David S.
            - Reece, B. Carroll
            - Romney, Vernon
            - Tate, Ben A.
          - Copies replies from Taft office
          - “A Man of Courage”
      - Appel, Monte
      - Associated Press v. Taft
      - Background material, (2 folders); (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 426, Box 427, Box 428, Box 429)
      - Barnes, Earl (Box 430)
      - Bell, Jack
      - Bender, George
      - Bliss, Ray
      - “Bob Taft Wins Election”
      - Brewer, Basil, (3 folders)
      - Carr, Eugene
      - Chicago, Ill., convention (Box 431)
        - Analysis of
        - Arrangements
        - Details
        - Incoming correspondence
          - June, undated, (4 folders)
          - July, 1-14, undated, ( folders) (Box 432)
        - Notes
        - Outgoing correspondence (Box 433)
        - Tickets and badges
      - Citizens Committee
      - Citizens for Taft
      - Clippings, (3 folders) (Box 434)
      - Clubs
      - Coleman, Thomas E. (Box 435)
      - Colleges
      - Committee headquarters, publicity
      - Communism
      - Contributions
      - Correspondence, (2 folders); (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 436, Box 437)
      - Credentials
      - Delegates, (5 folders) (Box 438)
        - Card file (Box 439-440)
        - Chairman, volunteers, A-Z, (4 folders) (Box 441)
        - Mailing lists
      - Dentists
      - Desvernine, Raoul E.
      - Directory
      - Doctors (Box 442)
        - General, (2 folders)
        - National
      - Editors and publishers
      - Emanuel, Victor
      - Emison, Ewing
      - Engagements
        - Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minn., 1951, Sept. 22
        - North Dakota, 1951, Sept. 22
        - Detroit, Michigan, Founder's Day, 1951, Oct. 15 (Box 443)
        - New York, 1951, Oct. 17
        - Des Moines, Iowa, Iowa Banker Anniversary, 1951, Oct. 22
        - Sioux Falls, S.D., Chamber of Commerce, 1951, Oct. 23
        - Pittsburgh, Pa., 1951, Oct. 25
        - Knoxville, Tenn., 1951, Oct. 30
        - Providence, R.I., 1951, Oct. 31
        - Chicago, Ill., 1951, Nov. 2 (Box 444)
        - Alabama and Mississippi, 1951, Nov. 6
        - New Orleans, La., 1951, Nov. 7
        - Kansas City, Mo., 1951, Nov. 9
        - Oklahoma, Ok., 1951, Nov. 10
        - Dayton, Ohio, 1951, Nov. 12
        - Harrisburg, 1951, Nov. 13
        - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1951, Nov. 16
        - Cleveland, Ohio, 1951, Nov. 17
        - Chicago, Ill., 1951, Nov. 22
        - North Carolina, 1951, Nov. 27-29
        - Los Angeles, Calif., 1951, Dec. 5 (Box 445)
        - St. Louis, Mo., 1951, Dec. 7
        - Boston, Mass., 1951, Dec. 11
        - Richmond, Va.
        - Beloit and Monroe, Wis.
        - New York, N.Y.
          - 29 Club
          - Circus Saints and Sinners
          - Jan. 26
        - Florida, Orlando, Tampa, and St. Petersburg, Jan. 28, (2 folders) (Box 446)
        - Wilmington, Del., Jan. 31
        - Louisville, Ky., Feb. 2
        - Huntington and Charleston, W. Va., Feb. 4
        - Harrisonburg, Va., Feb. 5
        - Wisconsin Rapids, Wis., Feb. 9 (Box 447)
        - Spokane, Wash., Feb. 11
        - Seattle, Wash., Feb. 12
        - Portland, Ore., Feb. 13
        - Boise and Pocatello, Idaho, Feb. 14
        - Pendleton, Ore., Feb. 14
        - Cheyenne, Wy., Feb. 15 (Box 448)
        - Denver, Col., Feb. 16
        - Montpelier, Ver., Feb. 22
        - Cleveland, Ohio, Feb. 25
        - Illinois, Ill., Feb. 29
        - Wisconsin, Wis., Mar. 1-2
        - New Haven, Conn., Mar. 5
        - New Hampshire, Mar. 6-8 (Box 449)
        - Texas, Mar. 10-12
        - New Mexico, Mar. 13
        - Phoenix and Winslow Ariz., Mar. 14
        - Illinois, Mar. 15
        - Wisconsin, Mar. 17-30 (Box 450)
        - Illinois, Apr. 3-5
        - Williamantic, Conn., Apr. 14 (Box 451)
        - Pittsburgh, Pa., Apr. 15
        - Ann Arbor and Lansing, Mich., Apr. 16
        - Mass., Apr. 17-19
        - Warren, Ashtabula, Ravenna, Canton, Ohio, Apr. 21
        - District of Columbia, Apr. 23
        - Little Rock, Ark., Apr. 25
        - Missouri, Apr. 26
        - Cincinnati and Youngstown, Ohio, Apr. 27-28
        - Cleveland, Toledo, and Youngstown, Ohio, May 1-4
        - Wheeling and Fairmont, W. Va., May 7 (Box 452)
        - Hartford, Conn., Association of Boards of Education, May 8
        - Baltimore, Md., May 19
        - South Dakota, May 22-26
        - Buckhannon, W. Va., June 5
        - Indianapolis, Ind., June 6
        - New York, N.Y., June 12
        - Escanaba and Benton Harbor, Mich., Sept. 24
        - Racine, Wis., Sept. 25 (Box 453)
        - Chicago, Ill., Sept. 26
        - Kentucky, Sept. 29
        - Cleveland, Ohio, Oct. 1
        - Columbus, Ohio, Oct. 3
        - Illinois, Oct. 7
        - Shenandoah, Iowa, Oct. 8
        - Indiana, Oct. 9-10
        - Wyoming, Oct. 13
        - New Mexico, Oct. 14
        - Utah, Oct. 15
        - Nebraska, Oct. 16
        - West Virginia, Oct. 18
        - New Jersey, Oct. 22
        - Philadelphia, Pa., Oct. 23
        - Missouri, Oct. 25
        - Helena, Mont., Oct. 27
        - Washington, Oct. 28
        - Arizona, Oct. 29
        - Indiana, Oct. 30
        - Ohio, Nov. 1
        - Miscellaneous
      - Form letters
      - Farmer's list
      - Foreign policy
      - GOP's best bet for 1952
      - Governors lists
      - Gradison, Willis D.
      - Guylay, Richard L.
      - Hamilton, John D. M. (Box 454)
      - Here's What Happened in Texas
      - Hoffman, Nickerson
      - How the Taft-Hartley Law protects
      - Hollister, John B.
      - Ingalls, David S., (2 folders)
      - Insufficient addresses
      - Insufficient addresses (Box 455)
        - A-Z, (2 folders)
        - Miscellaneous
      - Issues
      - Itinerary and notes
      - Jewish
      - Johnston, Victor A.
      - Key men questionnaires
      - Klein, Julius
      - Labor
      - Lawyers
      - List of workers, (2 folders) (Box 456)
        - County
        - State
      - Literature (Box 457)
      - Manning, Helen Taft
      - Marshall, John
      - Martin, I. Jack
      - Ministers
      - “My Farm Stand”
      - National committee
      - Nationality groups
      - Negroes (Box 458)
      - Notebooks, state delegations, vols. 1-5, (2 folders)
      - Ohio, Apr. 21
      - Politicians
      - Polls and predictions, (2 folders) (Box 459)
      - Press releases, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 460)
      - Publicity
      - Quotes about Taft
      - Radio reports
      - Reece, B. Carroll
      - Reeves, Mildred E.
      - Reprints
      - Republican candidates, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 461)
      - Republican convention (Box 462)
      - Reservations
      - Romney, Vernon
      - Sage, DeWitt L.
      - Schedules and biographical sketches
      - Selvage, James P.
      - Senate minority memorandum
      - Slogans, (1 folder) (Box 463)
      - Speech material, (2 folders) (Box 464)
      - State workers, A-Z, (2 folders)
      - Tate, Ben E., (2 folders) (Box 465)
      - Teachers
      - “Texas Affairs”, (1 folder); (4 folders); (3 folders) (Box 466, Box 467, Box 468)
      - Transportation vouchers (Box 469)
      - Undelivered letters
      - Unidentified correspondence
      - Veterans, national
      - Victor, Riesel
      - Washington, office finances (Box 470)
      - Wedemeyer, Albert C.
      - Women
      - Workers for Taft, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 471)
      - Young Republicans Club
      - Younger, Cole
- Legislative Papers, 1920-1953 (Box 471-870)
  Legislative correspondence, position statements, local, state, and national Republican programs, and congressional committee hearings and reports.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person, organization, or subject and chronologically thereunder.
  - Ohio (Box 471)
    - Abolish direct primary campaign, 1926
    - Anti-Tax Amendment League, 1933
    - City and state campaign, 1925-1927
    - Classification amendment, 1929, (4 folders) (Box 472)
    - Coal matters, 1920
    - Currency, Gannett, 1935-1936 (Box 473)
    - Flood control, 1936-1937
    - Gongwer reports, 1935-1937, (3 folders)
    - Intangible tax (Box 474)
      - Law, litigations and briefs, 1932, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1932-1933, (2 folders)
    - Legislative session, 1931, (2 folders) (Box 475)
    - Miscellaneous matters
      - 1924-1925, (2 folders)
      - 1926-1936, (5 folders) (Box 476)
      - 1937 (Box 477)
      - Tax material
        - 1930-1931, (2 folders)
        - 1931, (2 folders) (Box 478)
    - New tax system
      - 1931-1932, (2 folders)
      - 1932-1933, (2 folders) (Box 479)
    - River pollution, 1938
    - School district bill, 1927
    - Special session, 1932, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 480)
    - State aid bill, 1927
    - State bond law, 1926-1927
    - Study of judicial administration, 1930
    - Tax, association, 1927-1931
    - Tax
      - Committee, legal subcommittee, 1930
      - Program, 1931
      - Revision, 1923-1931, (3 folders) (Box 481)
        - Miscellaneous material, 1930-1931
    - Taxation, 1925-1930, (2 folders) (Box 482)
      - Bond limitation, 1921
      - Smith law, substitutes, and modifications, 1920-1922
      - Sources, reports and memoranda, 1920-1921
  - United States Senate
    - Abolish Electoral College, 1951-1953
    - Administrative agencies, 1942-1946
    - Adverse letters, 1951
    - Agriculture, 1938-1941, (4 folders) (Box 483)
      - General, 1946-1947
      - Basic tests and data, 1942-1953, (3 folders) (Box 484)
      - Brannan, Charles, 1948, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 485)
      - Current, 1949-1953, (2 folders)
      - Farm policy, 1952
      - Farm speech material, 1950-1951 (Box 486)
      - Marketing quotas, 1941, (2 folders)
      - Planning, 1940-1949, undated, (2 folders)
    - Alaskan statehood (Box 487)
    - Aliens and immigration, 1944 See also containers 519-520, Displaced persons
    - Alley Dwelling Authority, 1939
    - Allocation-Export Control, 1948
    - American Veteran's Committee, 1946
    - Anti-discriminations, 1947
    - Anti-Jewish propaganda
      - 1938-1939, (2 folders)
      - 1939-1941 (Box 488)
    - Anti-Trumanism, 1949
    - Annapolis, Md. And West Point, N.Y., military academies, (2 folders)
    - Appointments
      - 1942
      - 1946 (Box 489)
    - Armament and national defense, 1938-1941, (3 folders)
    - Armed forces, 1949 (Box 490)
    - Armed services, 1950-1951, (2 folders)
      - Defense orders, 1952
      - European army, 1952
      - Universal military training, 1951-1952
    - Army relief, 1944
    - Army speech, 1952, (2 folders)
    - Army and selective service, 1946-1947 (Box 491)
    - Atomic energy, 1945-1948
      - Domestic control, (S 1717), 1946-1947
      - International control, 1946-1947
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1948-1949
    - Austria, 1948
    - Aviation, 1941
    - Aviation plans and treaties, 1944-1945, (3 folders) (Box 492)
    - Autocratic Power and Reorganization Bill, 1938
    - Baltic states, 1945-1946
    - Bankhead Amendment-textile price control, 1944 (Box 493)
    - Banking and currency, 1939-1946, (3 folders)
      - Barkley Bill S. 477
      - 1939 (Box 494)
      - Committee, 1943-1944
      - Devaluation and stabilization, 1939
      - General, 1939
    - Basing points, 1948-1953, (2 folders) (Box 495)
    - Bauxite, 1950
    - Berne Convention, 1939
    - Bigelow pension plan, 1939
    - Board of Economic Warfare, 1943
    - Bohlen, Charles E., 1951-1953
    - Book, 1951
    - Books in wartime, 1944 (Box 496)
    - Branch banking, 1941
    - Bretton Woods Agreement
      - 1943-1945, (3 folders)
      - 1945-1949, (4 folders) (Box 497)
    - Bricker, John W. (Box 498)
      - Campaign, 1943-1944, (3 folders)
      - Treaty S. J. Res. 1, 1952-1953, (2 folders)
    - Britain (Box 499)
      - Budget, taxes, 1949
      - Comparative efficiency, productivity, 1948-1949
      - Opinion of others, 1949
      - Trade devaluation, 1949
    - British
      - China trade, 1951
    - British trade loans, 1945-1947 (Box 500)
    - Broadcasts, 1939
    - Brown-Maybank Bill, 1945
    - Budget
      - General
        - 1939-1946, (3 folders)
        - 1946-1949, (4 folders) (Box 501)
        - 1949-1953, (2 folders) (Box 502)
      - Appropriations, 1939-1940, 1947-1951, (2 folders)
      - Finances, 1935-1939, (2 folders) (Box 503)
      - Joint Committee, 1947
    - Bulwinkle Bill (S. 110), 1947
    - Bureaucracy, 1938-1940
    - Bureaucratic abuse and procedural reform, 1944-1946
    - Burton, Harold H., 1945 (Box 504)
    - Business, 1938-1940
      - Examples, 1945, (3 folders)
      - Men, 1940-1941
    - Butler, Pierce, 1939
    - Cancer, 1946
    - Cancer research, 1947 (Box 505)
    - Catholic controversy, 1945-1950, (3 folders)
    - Child Care-Lanham Act, 1943-1944
    - Children's Emergency Fund (S. 3420), 1950 (Box 506)
    - China, 1945-1949, (2 folders)
      - Formosa, 1950
      - W. Bruce Pirnie, 1948-1950 (Box 507)
    - Cigarette tax evasion, 1949
    - Cincinnati, Ohio
      - Airport, 1942
      - Republican matters, 1945-1946
    - Civil rights, 1945-1949
    - Civil service retirement
      - 1946-1947
      - 1947-1948, (3 folders) (Box 508)
    - Civil service, Taft Bill and miscellaneous, 1943-1947
    - Cleveland, Ohio, Republican matters, 1945
    - Clippings, 1949
    - Coal (Box 509)
      - General, 1941-1951, (3 folders)
      - Taft Hartley, 1950, (2 folders)
    - Colored representation in army and navy, 1940-1944, (2 folders) (Box 510)
    - Commission
      - Federal aid, 1953, (2 folders)
      - Organization of executive branch of the government, 1953 (Box 511)
    - Committee
      - Committees, 1942-1951, (2 folders)
      - Education and labor, 1943
      - Finance
        - 1949-1951
        - 1951, (2 folders) (Box 512)
      - Territories, 1946
    - Commodity Credit Corp.
      - General
        - 1943, (1 folder)
        - 1945-1949, (2 folders) (Box 513)
      - Loans to Formosa, 1940
    - Communism
      - General
        - 1938-1947, (2 folders)
        - 1947-1953, (2 folders) (Box 514)
      - Books, 1942-1949, (2 folders)
    - Compulsory military training, 1945-1947 (Box 515)
    - Conant, James B., 1949-1953
    - Congress
      - Eightieth Congress, 1946
      - Maloney Committee, 1942-1946, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous, 1951-1952
    - Connally, Tom, post-war resolution, 1943
    - Conscription of Everybody, 1944
    - Conservation (Box 516)
      - American Forestry Association, 1939
      - General, 1938-1939
    - Controls, price and wage, 1952-1953
    - Copper and zinc, 1947-1950
    - Corporation reports, 1947
    - Credit, 1952
    - Crank letters, 1936-1940 (Box 517)
    - Current
      - Legislation, 1940
      - Literature, unfavorable, 1949, (2 folders)
      - Political, 1952
      - Cuyahoga River, 1943
    - Dayton, Ohio, critical area information, 1943 (Box 518)
    - Debt Limit Bill, 1945
    - Defense Production Act, 1951
    - Dental aid bills, 1944-1946
    - Department of Health, 1947
    - Department of Health, Education and Security Bill
      - 1947-1953
      - 1946-1947 (Box 519)